

RONNRICK B. ALCEDO

PROGRAMMER

CONTACT

- +63 946 399 6815
- ✓ alcedoronnrick@gmail.com
- General Trias Cavite

EDUCATION

2014 - 2016 BATANGAS STATE UNIVERSITY

- Bachelor of Science in Industrial Technology Major in Computer Technology
- Undergraduate

SKILLS

- HTML5
- MS Access
- CSS3
- Visual Basic
- Javascript
- MS Excel
- Vue Js
- Git
- Vuetify
- Git Hub
- PHP
- Git Lab
- Laravel
- Source Tree
- MS SQL
- Draw.io
- MySQL
- Attention to detail
- Good communication skills

ACHIEVEMENTS

 Most Outstanding Employee (2024)

PROFILE

Secure a career opportunity to fully utilize my skills and expand my knowledge and gain practical experience specifically in terms of web development and programming, while making a significant contribution to the success of the company.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Programmer

2022 - PRESENT

HRD Singapore Pte., Ltd.

- Developed innovative web-based systems that enhance users production capabilities.
- Maintained and enhanced internal desktop applications, boosting efficiency with Visual Basic and MS Access.
- Utilize various servers to manage databases, including MS SQL and MySQL.
- Making detailed system documentation that is lined with production processes, enhancing efficiency and productivity.
- Conduct test cases as software release requirements.

Production Staff

2016 - 2022

PV Tech Pte., Ltd.

- Collaborated with production staff to optimize loading schedules and minimize delays.
- Developed and maintained strong relationships with logistics and transportation teams to ensure timely deliveries.
- Conducted regular checks of the materials to be loaded to ensure the quality to meet customer satisfaction.
- Implemented quality control measures to reduce errors in material handling and loading.
- Maintained accurate records of materials loaded, including quantities and types, for inventory management.

REFERENCE

Lester Prodigalidad

HRD Singapore Pte., Ltd.

Team Head

Phone: 09069207981

Email: lester.prodigalidad.lp@gmail.com

Edan Jarlo Tanfelix

HRD Singapore Pte., Ltd.

Section Head

Phone: 09158757729

Email: ejarlotanfelix@gmail.com